Let’s continue repairing together
careful
Ahhh
ah
Dalian's iron cloth shirt can't be torn
Why does the strength increase so quickly?
ah
Magic Box Touching Fist
Who did you fight with just now?
behind the back
Miss Senior Brother
I'll go find him
then then that tree
He's at that door
Oops, report back to Uncle Master
we patrol here
But on the cliff
Saw Zhenguan coming out of a secret door
Then he attacked us without any explanation.
Go on
I'm afraid all the details about my lady will be exposed.
That figure
It is indeed the Zhenguan disciple who was expelled from the mountain gate before.
Recognize his face
But I always feel like there are some strange changes in him
Um
You guys go back to the Monk Monastery first.
Just leave it to me here
It's Uncle Master, Uncle Master
Oh, thank you so much, uncle, for helping me just now
ah
It turns out that this is the strength that is close to the peak of outdoor scenes.
So handsome oops
It scared me to death just now
Fortunately, Xuanbei Shishu arrived in time
xuanbei poetry book
Yes, that was Master Xuanbei just now
I heard a senior brother mentioned it before
Is he great?
Master Xuanbei
It's Xuanzi quilt
The first eminent monk to step into the eighth layer of the outdoor scene
Only one step away from the peak
Exterior view of Eighth Heaven
Brother, I really want to become such a master
Brother, you can definitely be gentle.
Just got beaten
The bones are falling apart
Are you two okay?
The signal just now was sent by you
Xuanxin means that Zhenguan just appeared in the back mountain
surprise attack on us
Zhenguan
Why is he here?
I do not know
Thanks to Master Xuanbei for helping me
I guess I've chased him by now
Why
When you go down the mountain, you still have the chance to start over again.
Why is Zhenguan so obsessed with staying here?
Just be fine
You two, hurry up and catch up with me.
I wasn’t Master Xuanxin a few days ago
Did you drive Senior Brother Zhenguan down the mountain in person?
Why are you back now?
Don't know
Go back first
Oh, right
You have to compete with Senior Brother Zhenmiao tomorrow
Where did he get the confidence to challenge Brother Zhenmiao again?
Just a handyman
An evil monk
I won against Senior Brother Zhenliang last time
I think it's purely a coincidence
Hey, you still have some skills, huh?
I don’t know how high the sky is and how high it is
Ahhh
Ah, senior brother
Why is Master Xuanbei here too?
The contempt of Brother Zhenmiao and Zhending
It was spread throughout the hospital
Could Senior Brother Xuanbei not know?
I guess
He also wanted to come and see with his own eyes the true strength.
Please give me some advice, Brother Zhenmiao.
You make the first move
No, can't give up
Plastic surgery
Senior brother
I haven't given up yet
Ahhh
ah
I don't even recognize it
It's Senior Brother Zhenchang
Senior Brother Zhenchang is back
back again
Ah, he is Senior Brother Zhenchang
Um
Senior Brother Zhenzhen who is truly prepared by the three major disciples
Some time ago he passed through Tongren Lane
Became the youngest wandering disciple
It's just a discussion between brothers
Remember the key points till now
Thanks for the teaching, senior brother
Sorry, junior brother
uncle
I'm really sure of the move this guy just used.
The five-story courtyard didn’t teach it at all.
Where did he learn this secretly?
really
His few steps were weird
Never seen it before
Does our golden cicada have such a move?
Could it be that the theft of Zangxing Pavilion had something to do with him?
Why are there people everywhere who like to make snitches?
I have seen the Xuanbei history book
You must ask where you learned the Eight Immortals
can not say
I can only take one step and see one step.
Your pace
Where did you get it from?
Returning poems and books on xuanbei is a family tradition
Before becoming a monk, the disciple had been exposed to many ancestral martial arts
On weekdays, when I have nothing to do, I will practice
Wow, it seems he believes it
Hum ok
Too scheming
Talking wildly
You will be punished by facing the wall for 3 days
For today’s written test, let’s not do the counting first.
Brother, are you okay?
Let's go, I'll be locked up
It will be great now that the normal senior brother is back
Why did Senior Brother Zhenchang come with you?
Maybe you're afraid that if I don't go to confinement, I'll take the opportunity to escape.
Ha ha
I don't like excitement
Dare I ask my junior brother’s dharma number?
Report back to senior brother
The Dharma Name is True
poetry calligraphy
You are facing the wall just to give everyone an explanation
You don't have to take it too seriously
I do not mind
got used to
Hey, senior brother, where did you go during this wandering trip?
First time traveling down the mountain
Not far to go
The farthest is only as far as Jiangzhou City
Ah, senior brother
What is there in Jiangzhou city?
Gu Huaizhi, who is on the top of the earth rankings
He is the lord of Jiangzhou City
Jiangzhou City was built on the riverside
Looks like a giant dragon from a distance
There are even eight levels and nine trees in the city.
Heavy traffic
Since coming to this world
I haven’t been anywhere yet.
I don’t know if there will be a chance in the future.
But no matter how nice it is outside
It's just a mirror, a flower in the water, a moon in the water
Not as relaxed as in Jinchan
We are well fed and clothed in the temple.
You can also practice kung fu
Why are you going out?
Wall facing three blades
I’m worried that I can’t find a place to practice alone.
Opportunity for the Eight Steps of Divine Walking
Ha, I’m finally a little more proficient.
Little monk takes orders
Isn’t martial arts making a lot of progress?
The young monk doesn’t want to see the Buddha in his prime.
I know you are at Jinchan Temple
A street where it’s hard to get a sharp edge
So I prepared some for you
I have to thank Miss Jiang for that.
I knew it
Miss Jiang still thinks that I am really my junior brother.
Stay safe
Senior Brother Zhang and Senior Brother Qi
New people will join this mission
Ah hey
What is this place
You, who are you?
What to look at
I'll kill you
why am i here
Sample tricks
Junior Brother Zhending’s skills have really improved rapidly.
Dare to ask this master
What's going on?
What to bet on?
Tell me if you have a bet
Hahaha
Several of you should have noticed the difference here.
It’s normal now
The poor monk is not much different from you.
I just came to this trial time a while ago
Trial World
I'm here to find out if there's any other way out of here.
master master
Master, please, boy.
elementary school girl
The little girl has no power to tie the chicken
But Feng Yu talks about the Lord of Six Paths
let me go back
I will keep my word
Why is this woman so abnormal?
LOL
Amitabha
Donor, do you think I have the final say?
master master
Please love me
Ahhh
Lord of the Six Paths
I really got an ordinary girl who doesn’t know how to do martial arts.
ah
Task started
The Northern Barbarians took over the Central Plains
Taoism goes against the teacher and slaughters the people
The monks of Jinchan Temple rose up to resist
General fruit catechu to scare martial arts
Place an eyeliner in Jinzen Temple
Lead many masters to Shaohua Mountain
Encirclement and Suppression of Jinchan Temple
Main mission one
The troops were divided into two groups to break through and intercept
Send the internal list to Jinzen Temple within three days
Later, he was obliterated all the way to Jinzen Temple.
Those who have not been treated within the time limit
Each person who successfully enters the temple will be rewarded with 50 good deeds.
Let me sweep across
young heartbeat
you know