Let’s continue repairing together
Hero, let me help you
ah
What happened to the Seventh Senior Brother?
I was in crisis as soon as I woke up
Uh-huh
It's too late for you to say that, huh?
The Lord of the Six Paths said that the troops should be divided into two groups.
Sure enough, Zhang Yuanshan and Miss Jiang are not here.
Why do I have to be connected with this poker?
If only I could team up with Miss Jiang
Talking and laughing along the way
that would be nice
Forget it, that's all
Let me first slap the poker face on you and apologize.
Hahahaha, senior brother Qin
I saw you were looking graceful just now
It seems that the Long River Sunset Sword Technique has achieved some success.
No strong enemy
Dare not agree
That’s eight more words
What if you were a robot talking and wasting electricity?
Hahahahahaha, God is so powerful
Shen Sang knows that his name is Xiang Hui
Please also be kind to me
Take good care of yourself
Uh haha
Let’s go to Jinchan Temple
Do you want to go with us or by yourself?
Of course, that little guy is following the holy monk closely.
I'm waiting for you
You just showed off your magical powers
Fall into the Tiger Taming Flying Palace
That's it. Okay, okay, okay.
you're almost done
don't leave me
Why
If you are willing to follow, that is
These two people must be a burden with them.
But I want to introduce the emperor list again before
If Miss Jiang hadn’t disdained my low martial arts skills,
If you take care of me all the way, I'm afraid I'll go to the West long ago
I don’t know how he is doing now.
This should be the last few
Without further ado
Let’s set off quickly to Chaohua Mountain
Will the little monk and the others be okay?
The truth is no longer what it used to be
What's more, there are knights delivering
no need to worry
It’s a long way to Shaohua Mountain
Several assassins came on horseback just now
Just available
The journey is quite long
His senior brother
Could it be that we already know the location of Shaohua Mountain?
This place is the only way for Huahua Sect to go to Jinchan Temple.
This road is smooth
It takes at least five days to go up Shaohua Mountain
There is another shortcut
But forced to sit southbound
Could it be that the geographical environment of this world
It’s the same as the world we live in
There is only one way to go
What happened to the little benefactor?
master me
I don’t know how to ride this?
Master, can I learn to ride?
don't leave me
Why
Hey, donor, if you don’t mind
You can pay for it with me
Um
let him sit behind me
What if he plots against me like in the TV series?
Grandmaster
Hey boy girl
You'd better sit in the front
Xiaoseng is worried that you will be thrown away, huh?
Amitabha
Color is empty
Empty without color
Form is empty
Emptiness is form
So
ah
We'd better leave quickly
Let's catch up with Brother Cavalry and the others.
Seventh Senior Brother
There is one more thing that bothers me
Are you worried about the mission of Allah of the Six Paths?
good
As the mission says
All the way to Houdao Jinzen Temple will be obliterated
Could it be that we and Miss Jiang and the others cannot have both?
The rules are established
It’s useless to think too much
holy monk
It’s important that we hurry up
another team
He will definitely try his best to get ahead of us
Wait until they enter Jinzen Temple
We can't go to the West anymore.
There must be some other way
Seventh Senior Brother
After traveling for so long, how far is Huashan?
Can keep up with Seventh Senior Brother
Actually, you can say two more words per sentence
Hey, look at this trial mission
You must have a bitter look on your face
Have to do it too
You have a smile on your face, so let’s do it too, right?
Then why don't you smile?
relax
What about your swordsmanship?
Wouldn't it be a better chance of rebirth?
Hey dear mother
Am I a counselor for autistic children?
Hahahahaha
What the holy monk said is absolutely true
What you said is absolutely true, hahaha
Amitabha
The so-called everything gained
All from the beginning
Seventh Brother, we must learn to smile
A senior once said that when you smile
The world will fall in love with you, this lovelorn world
What if he falls in love with us?
Then can’t we accomplish this task?
I feel very relaxed
My face was born like this
It's going to rain
Find a place to take shelter from the rain
Little monk, come here
If the mission issued by the Lord of Six Paths
Aligned with your bottom line
So what?
as you said before
Now we have Senior Brother Zhang
They probably must have
Are you willing to kill for them?
Become a Buddha immediately
At the last minute
Naturally you will know
Seventh senior brother
What did you just say?
Smiling in the face of a passionate kiss, right?
At this time, you still have to joke casually
It just shows that our path is in the right direction.
This heavy rain is pouring
I got wet and couldn't put a few things in my spare time.
I'm afraid there will be a close fight next.
Force me to stay here and deal with them again.
Junior Brother Truth
This place is not far from Jinzen Temple
It should be safe in front
Don't take it lightly
Brother Zhang, tell me
If we had really arrived at Jinzen Temple earlier,
What should the little monks do?
The gun captain still has time to care about others
I've been really unlucky for eight lifetimes
Why did you come to this damn place?
hey what is
He is not human
Ansheng is afraid of being killed by the dead
yeah
When the clouds disperse, is there anyone waiting?
Let me sweep across
Burn the road again and make it salty
can also feel it