Let’s continue repairing together
Seventh Senior Brother, are you okay?
We have to get into the mountains as soon as possible
Many enemies escaped
Afraid of help coming
Also look for the bodies of Xiao Hui and Xiaozi.
I'm afraid the two of them will meet each other
Master
Boy, girl, are you okay?
They're all here to attack you
Are you injured?
I'm lying on the ground and no one is paying attention to me.
As long as you're fine
Oh, I'm so lucky that you two are protecting each other.
I think we will arrive at Jinzen Temple soon.
You're fine too
your face
Haha, just a minor injury
After being stabbed, he fainted and fell to the ground.
But take a life
If I had known I would have pretended to be dead
Let's go. It's getting late.
Let’s find a place to rest first, hahaha
The three-day period is getting closer and closer
I don’t know where Miss Jiang and Senior Brother Zhang are.
Little monk, don't come here
Don't arouse me
Little monk
Master, we have to prepare to go down the mountain.
The rumor is at the foot of the mountain next door
master me
Are you talking in your sleep?
Are you calling Xiao Sang?
Master, please be careful in the future
A girl named Gu Xiaosang
He is the baddest, baddest villain in the world
Oh why
All in all, very bad, very bad
Kill without blinking an eye
It will be completed for three days at Haishi today.
not much time
Set off quickly
The gentleman has passed
Hurry up the mountain
Excuse me
What do you mean?
The situation with Miss Jiang and Senior Brother Zhang is unknown now.
If we go up the mountain and enter the temple
Wouldn't it be putting them to death?
But maybe they were already ahead of us.
yes
And the Northern Barbarian army will not stop and wait for us.
Yes, everything you mentioned is sick.
In both our hands
It's like holding a control
The organ of life and death of the opponent
In order to prevent the other party from pressing it first
the only way
Just be that ruthless person first
But I believe in Miss Jiang and Senior Brother Zhang
They will also believe us
It's barely enough for the spider to meet the boy.
If Brother Seventh also insists on going up the mountain, I'm afraid
Seventh Senior Brother
You asked me before if I was willing to kill myself as an adult
This moment is my answer
What is the real plan?
If we wait for someone in this huge Shaohua Mountain
I will definitely choose a conspicuous place
If it were Miss Jiang, they would definitely think so too.
You go to the temple gate first
Maybe Miss Jiang and the others are already waiting for us there.
I'll check privately to see if there are any other clues
It’s still like there was no news before
Then we'll keep it private
Aren't you afraid that I'll go ahead with them two privately?
six paths
Since it is said that the team that arrives first will complete the task
Then there is a possibility
It is necessary for all the surviving team members to be present.
and i believe you
Haha
Several people described by senior brother
Really no impression
Oh, it's getting late already
But since I'm not obliterated yet
They must be waiting for me somewhere
Miss Jiang, I will definitely find you
Could it be that the master is also a friend in the world of martial arts?
Are you here to help Jinzen Temple?
The donor knows that there are other people who come here to have a destiny
In Xiahe Luo Wei Wuji
Come to Shengyuan Jinchan Temple from all walks of life
The heroes who resisted the Manchus
Now everyone is gathering at the mountain inn within the inn
30 years of Luohe wine
Mellow and fragrant
Indeed extraordinary
It's a pity that the world is in chaos
The time to enjoy tea and wine with peace of mind is running out.
The way of the world is extremely victorious and will eventually lead to death and rebirth.
We need to remain useful
for recovery
Mr. Zhang’s insights are indeed extraordinary
Brothers got together
They were responsible for this Manchu invasion.
glo boil
There are heroes with high moral character and high prestige who rush to protect heroes.
I look at that catechu
Abundance as a tool
Why
Among these highly respected heroes
I'm afraid there's you, Master Wei.
Ha ha ha ha
No soup, no soup
You two gentlemen, what would you like to eat?
Uh-huh
I have been studying martial arts for thirty years
But it is worth noting that there is no way to innate the door
I told Mr. Zhang that I
The weak crown has broken through the innate
And this time, I went through many obstacles for the sake of Jin Chan.
Come here to report to Mr. Zhang
There
He was saying goodbye to Young Master He Luomen and was learning how to taste tea.
You guys should talk about the old days first
A little tired in the middle of the night
I'm going to order some shit.
Let’s talk about it when we come
ah
Who is this monk?
Can monks also drink alcohol?
The dead man knew Mr. Zhang
Is he also some kind of film and television master?
Do it first to respect
Oops
Forget my body
He is a monk who only eats vegetarian food.
For real
Don’t talk about the commandments
You shouldn’t be so reckless when you drink for the first time
Don’t know the taste of strong liquor
How can a young monk understand the value and necessity of precepts?
Yeah, no exception
I've been waiting for you for a long time
The zombie girl was right
As expected, you are also looking for our gun girl.
little monk
You came
Even Miss Jiang
Who is this person?
Junior Brother Zhending
He is the disciple of his mentor and good friend
Nicknamed the Leaf-cutting Buddha Knife
This is a trick
It turns out that he is also an expert outside the world.
You are so stingy at your age
He's young but he's got a lot of tricks up his sleeve
His senior brother is waiting for us at the gate of the temple
Without further ado
Let's go quickly
Seventh Senior Brother
Seventh Junior Brother
Where is the boy?
Oh, it's convenient to go to the master
You are finally back
Hahaha I'm really nervous now
I'm afraid it's not that easy to die.
Mistress has a way
who
Breaking into Jinzen Temple without authorization
Don't blame us for being rude.
Senior brother, I am Zhending from a miscellaneous hospital.
You don’t recognize me anymore
Wanwan looked at what he was wearing
It's true that they destroyed the hospital.
do you know
I don’t know you then
Meet uh
Do you know me or not?
This is the kind of senior brother
I met these donors on the road
I learned there was a shocking conspiracy
We must report it to the abbot as soon as possible
Brother, please let them in
Thank you for your hard work, junior brother
Come in quickly
Don't delay the business
Even if you arrive at Jinchan Temple
Once the main mission is completed
Each person will be rewarded with 50 good deeds
Mission 2: Hold on to the golden toad until the last moment
Success reward 100 good deeds
Otherwise erase
we we did it
no one was wiped out
we did it
Well, who are you?
Ahhh
Everyone
I'm waiting to get the list of Duocate tea restaurants.
It's urgent
He also asked to see the scheming master's strange behavior and behavior.
I look at you like it's hard
let them in
Master Deguang, eh
Is this Zhang Shaoxia who killed Guan Haoran?
Chang Ha Fang has heard about it for a long time
Please come with me
Several donors risked their lives to retaliate
I am very grateful
This road is really dangerous
Fortunately, he lived up to his expectations
Finally got this urgent information
Brought to the abbot
ah
Temptation of mortal world
Monks who are always monastics are not immune to this
There was a traitor in the temple after all.
I really want to thank you all this time.
Master Abbot’s magical skills are unparalleled
Defeat all doubts
I'm just icing on the cake.
The power of Duocatecha is unpredictable
I just wanted to give up my remaining body
It’s just the determination not to fear life and death.
Fang Chang promises to be extremely hateful
Never keep a useful person
Come to the future with pictures
Amitabha
As monks you are
Why can't you see through this stupid sentence?
Then go die
Xiaohui
Hahahaha, the general asked me to say hello to the abbot.
So fast
He is a versatile scholar
The ever-changing scholar
Could it be that
What's going on with Xiang Hui, little monk?
I'm afraid he is no longer Xiang Hui.
The real Xiang Hui was in our woods when we were previewing
Already killed by this ever-changing scholar
What's the use of being stronger?
You're not being fooled around by me
Hahahahaha
If the beating continues, I won't be able to escape immediately.
careful
Extraordinary
There is a wonderful synergy with the eight parts of body and mind
Boundless sea of ​​suffering
The donor has not turned around yet.
Ha ha ha ha
If Master Abbot can lead Zhongtou City
The general will surely make Jinchan Temple the first Buddhist temple
Incense continues
otherwise
Thousand-year foundation of Jinchan Temple
Will be destroyed in half
Amitabha
My thousand-year foundation of Jinchan Temple
Only in the mansion, the Zen battle is about to begin
Forgive me
Can't stay behind
Do you dare to commit murder?
Buddha has a compassionate heart
There are also King Kong nightmares
Straight line Ren Wuyi
Kill the ever-changing scholar Zhang Yuanshan Zhending
Reward 30 good deeds
Qi Zhengyan Jiang Zhiwei
Each reward is 20 bows
Straight line mission 2 starts
kill the general
The flowers are long
Square Anthurium
Anthurium
ah
You spies
What else is there?
No, they are spies
I'm afraid I've passed away just now.
His origin as a benefactor is unclear
extraordinary moment
Please leave the temple early
We traveled through mountains and rivers to save Jinchan Temple
But this suspicion
Could it be that other consciousnesses came from the mountains?
Chilling?
So I'll take my leave first.
If anyone can help
Please ask the abbot for instructions
Companion Revenant
Please also ask the abbot to supervise