This world is extremely desolate or chaotic
Faith also turns to dust
Full of wounds, escape from this cage and swallow up the pain
Losing control under the pressure of endless fear
Losi, I will cherish this sword.
This level is the last level of the first level
After passing, we can go to the second floor. It's useless.
The first trial of choosing the master
Can only be completed by the owner alone
before i lose patience
Let me play with you
Hu Luozhan did a good job
I don't recognize you
This kid contains all the phenomena of heaven and earth.
I don't know if you can bear it
ah
Captain, what is this?
Reward?
This change is so swollen
Master, I will take back this lilac flower first, Master.
The two of them now let me take over
I can call them whenever I need them
Oh, this is the reward for falling out of love
It’s so cool to summon a top boss to be your younger brother
Examination 2
Congratulations on passing the first level of all broken loves
12Holiness is my strongest act
All of them are beyond the ninth level.
And what you faced before
It's because they were suppressed based on your current strength
threats after
In the future, as your strength improves
Their strength will gradually recover
The second level has been opened for you
each subsequent layer
There will be different holy places waiting for you.
Without further ado, Captain
They quickly went to the second floor to continue fighting.
not that simple
Go higher and higher
It should be more difficult to defeat the Holy Throne
Let’s not take any chances just yet.
By the way, how are you doing with your cultivation?
They all work hard
Now it has exceeded 6,000 points
Hum, we are very itchy now
When will we leave for Sand Demon Clan?
Wait a moment
The bright moon is calling me, he seems to be evolving again
Really? What will his evolution be like?
Can the leader take us with him?
I also want to see what Haoyue’s world is like
Hahaha
Is this the feeling of traveling back and forth?
Damn, don't squeeze me
Yes, the bad thing is the Haoyue Incident
you're the cross
rainbow
Where are the others?
good luck
are you hungry
This is your favorite dried fish
This is Haoyue’s memory event
This little guy is so naughty
nobody
It was just my misunderstanding
I don’t know where the others were sent.
Even the soul chain can't contact me
We can only follow this little guy first
See what you find
Don't eat too much bullshit
Is the little guy okay?
The little guy has suffered so much
Little guy, why are you so seriously injured?
his injury
This is how it all came about
After bidding farewell to the court master
No matter the desperado
The gods here can punish you
Your body
The naked nigger man
The skin of the ghost is humiliated and the electricity can’t wait for help today
The evil of humiliation
The Heroic Soul of Our Lady of Heroes
That monarch and his ministers
Please give me the anger you are waiting for
Pour it all on Oziting Cliffen and resist the promise
Where is this?
Search for the memory in the fate cauldron
Such a smell
The truth of the world will emerge before the Lord’s eyes
Haochen
Cai'er
Yes, which
bright moon
Cai'er, how did everyone get here?
When we arrived at Haoyue's world, you disappeared.
Later I saw the zombies gathered at the foot of a mountain
When I arrived, I found you and Haoyue
Sorry Cai'er
make you worry
How is the situation outside now?
during your coma
We encountered an onslaught of living zombies
Everyone is resisting outside
Head, Head, Head, are you okay?
It's okay. Are you okay?
Where are the others?
ah
353How much are you?
Come on, come on, okay?
Before the completion of the Haoyue Project
The attacks of undead creatures will be endless.
Let’s go to Haochen together
It seems that a lot of spiritual energy was consumed during the divorce period
Leader, didn’t you just recruit two top bosses?
How about giving it a try?
What's the master's order?
Clear the battlefield this order
Oh my God, what happened? They were all killed instantly. That's it.
It’s a perfect holy place, it’s just a piece of shit.
I'll beat up the grandpa who's not even sixth level enough.
Crazy Killing Shura Slash
Ah, this guy is too fierce, right?
flower of ice and snow
Zero degree encounter
Frozen for thousands of miles
cold weather side
The owner is satisfied
Ah, the leader
How did you conquer these two monsters?
ah
Kill with me
Be careful everyone
The Zombie King has miraculous peak combat power
Let's defeat him together
Wang Yuanyuan
Sima Qian, you and Han Yu guard the entrance of the cave together.
The rest will join me in resisting the Zombie King. I am the leader.
Phoenix on all sides
Let this guy have a taste
3 times more powerful than the Gate of Creatures
Give me all your energy
Is this kid okay?
Captain, we are fine
kill osking griffan
Let's all sing "King of Ganjiujiang" together
Hanyu protects everyone
The government is here to try and I will lead your soldiers.
Demons and monsters
Avoid my edge
necessary
Korean are you okay?
can't hurt me
What
When people come, they can drive head-on with me
I have feelings
The first form of the six-path tour
Ma Tianxue
What happened to Linglong?
I can use it again for 6 bucks, no need
Tsai'er
Haochen let me come
Holy warrior is a new skill I acquired
There's no way I'm going to let you get any closer
catch him
Shen Yun
Xianyang Three Wonders
soaring climb
Is this the power of God?
leader
ah
Head of Team Head of Team Head of Team
Huiyue
They are 4 great kings
let
We use medicine to save lives
Favorite and follow
Don't get lost
You guys are looking at it so carefully
You must have understood the QR code scanning process by heart.
let us conceive
His Royal Highness is in charge of Dongying
Used and delicious
After rate upgrade
The danger of the mission will be doubled
You should practice more and come back for the assessment.
You approve our group’s assessment
But if one of us fails the assessment
Not only did our team fail
And voluntarily downgraded to another level
It’s useless, how can you chase after me better than me?