Senior brother, witness
the true Swallow Skims Clouds.
Impressive qinggong.
Let Ouyang Fei trade blows.
We’ll trap a turtle in a jar.
Luo Qiutong’s heartless.
Senior brother—
can we survive tonight?
Surrender now—
or it’s death.
Oh no!
Oh!
Lord Guan—
Zheng Dongting’s sword is divine.
Our sects’ brothers
can’t break through.
Wound salve’s running low.
Keep fighting, and the Arrest Alliance must order from Jiangnan Apothecary.
Our funds were wiped out.
Pond Master Yu Yaoxia has arrived!
Pond Master—
long journey.
Lord Guan—
too kind.
Fought all night—
not one death.
Zheng Dongting pulls his strikes.
He’s just sly.
Wounded enough
to drain our medicine.
No one dares charge.
He lingers a bit longer.
Lord Guan’s right.
I’ve relayed the message—
they’re here.
So quick?
Pond Master—
world’s top qinggong.
Compared to Zheng Dongting,
mine’s embarrassing.
Too humble.
After tonight,
no one outruns you.
Thanks for the reward, Hall Master Guan.
Junior brother—
thinking of Qiutong?
Knew it.
Senior brother—
If I die in Shezhou,
will Qiutong mourn me?
Say that to me, fine—
don’t tell outsiders.
I have face.
Zheng Dongting, Zu Beiqiu—
one last chance.
Bind yourselves and surrender.
The Arrest Alliance will summon elders for trial.
We’ll give you justice.
Pah!
Divine Hand breeds fleeing heroes—
no bound cowards.
Then—
today’s your death day.
Senior brother—
who’re you thinking of? Me?
Bro—
Hahahahaha!
My eleventh concubine.
Oh!
Senior brother—what?
Donors—
sins committed,
where to flee?
Bitter sea boundless—
turn back to shore.
Come on!
Amitabha.
Buddha’s mercy.
Senior brother—someone’s catching up!
So huge
yet so agile.
Please—
Ah!
Senior brother—
still alive?
Bad luck.
Even Nephew Lian changed his mind.
Perfect.
If Zheng Dongting gets desperate
and risks his kung fu—
we’ll need Nephew Lian too.
No need now.
Please—
I swear never to use seven sects’ arts.
He’s holding back.
Wait—with his skills, how’d he massacre the Luo clan?
No one saw him strike.
You only saw
him toss their banner into the fire.
Did I misjudge?
Luo massacre wasn’t him.
That’s what he wants.
No witnesses—
he denies forever.
If he fights now,
he’s trapped.
Divine Hand disciples—
ruthless and sly.
Arhat—
Arhat Formation.
Something new.
Runs on the array eye—
that’s the flaw.
You know how to break it?
Master hated Arhat Formation.
No clue why.
Beiqiu—remember it.
Teach those monks for me.
Who’s the eye?
They swap often—let me see.
Long-browed monk—
lips moving. Him.
Senior brother—switched!
Big monk—
eyes darting.
Switched!
Little old man.
Old man strength?
Senior brother—switched!
I know—I see.
Senior brother—that’s not it!
You said darting eyes—
cross-eyed always look like that.
Hey!
Junior brother—untie the ropes! Ah!
Junior brother—Minor Formless Skill!
Ah!
Senior brother—I can’t hold it!
What demon art?
Well done.
Why let them go?
Masters are wise—
know when to stop. Mercy.
Lord Guan—
next move?
Pond Master—have scouts
track the twin terrors.
Sure—but extra pay.
We’ve lost all face for the sects.
Lord Guan—wild idea:
Gui Xiang Brothel?
What?
Insane?
But they rushed there urgently.
Men, you know.
Brother Ouyang—no impure thoughts.
Qi sinks,
channels clog—
harder to move.
Nephew Lian—what’s your view?
Zheng Dongting’s swift—
headed to Lingnan.
Monk flees, temple stays.
Changqing—
to Yizhou.
Invite the Zu family to Xuzhou’s Kill Prestige Hall.
Yes, Lord Guan.
No—don’t harm families!
No choice.
Luo clan slaughtered whole—
Anyone help me?
[Watch Datang Ride the Wind every Thursday 10 AM]
[Scan for surprises and perks!]
Where you from?
Old Master Zu—
your son’s in trouble.
Hero Gang.
Hero Gang’s secret.
I know you.
North’s vast—
for ambitious men.
Go north?
Walking into the tribunal.
Who dares fight in Yizhou?
Dare dance here?
Zu Gui—grab blades.
To Xuzhou—collect debt.
Senior brother—slow down!
Nature good at first—
how’d wandering turn you villain?
Can’t eat it.
Chocolate joy—don’t go!